Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/latoya-bonk-msn-dnpc-rn-8324888b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

ACLS

PALS

Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

First Aid/CPR/AED Instructor

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Latoya Bonk MSN DNPc RN

Registered Nurse, Nursing Director

Greater Philadelphia Area

Summary

Experienced Nursing Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the Emergency/Trauma & Behavior Health specialty areas of urban and suburban hospitals. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, Nursing Education, Nursing Leadership, and Nurse Management of inpatient and outpatient adult and pediatric populations.

Experience

Healthcare

Director Of Nursing - Emergency Dept and Behavioral Health January 2020 - Present (7 months)

Greater Philadelphia

Trinity Health Mid-Atlantic
Nursing Manager
May 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 9 months)

Penn Medicine, University of Pennsylvania Health System Registered Nurse - Emergency Dept/Psych March 2014 - December 2019 (5 years 10 months)

Providing triage, assessments, and bedside interventions for patients with life threatening illnesses in a Level One Trauma Center, while collaborating with Emergency Department staff to provide comprehensive care to patients of varying acuity levels from pediatric to geriatric. Resource for staff nurses in the department.

UHS

Nurse Manager

December 2017 - April 2018 (5 months)

Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

Nurse manager of 2 adult medical psych/detox units and 1 adolescence unit with 24 inpatient beds each. Management of Registered Nurses and Techs during 24 hour hospital operations. Management and monitoring of Quality and assurance of regulatory unit based practices. Works with team

Page 1 of 2

members to monitor patient satisfaction and develop appropriate interventions. Management of performance of employee evaluations and disciplinary action; Monitoring of employee time and attendance via Kronos. Collaboration and involvement in hospital based committees.

Mercy Health System of Southeastern Pennsylvania Registered nurse - Emergency dept December 2011 - November 2014 (3 years)

Charge Nurse role and triage. Management of the critical care patient, supervising of ancillary staff, triage and stabilization of trauma patients including pediatric and neurologically unstable, Assisting in critical care transfers to higher level hospitals of care, nurse orienting and training of the newly hired nurses in the department.

Penn Medicine, University of Pennsylvania Health System Nurse Extern - Registered Nurse 2009 - 2012 (3 years)

Greater Philadelphia Area

Care of the pre and labor patient . Care of the high risk mother in baby including multiples, high risk cardiac compromised, immuno compromised and diverse populations. Perinatal evaluation center care and labor room care of mother and baby including fetal monitoring .

Education

Drexel University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.N), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2007 - 2011)

Holy Family University

MSN, Nursing Administration/Education · (2015 - 2017)

Holy Family University

Doctor of Nursing Practice , Educational Leadership and Administration,

General · (2018 - 2020)